# Curriculum Vitae

### **Personal Detail:**

Name: Hanadi Fraih AL-Mohammed

CPR: 880109629

Date of birth: 23/1/1988

Nationality: Bahraini

Driving license: yes

Cell phone: 35060214-34454464

E-mail: <u>hanadi882010@hotmail.com</u>

Language: excellent written and spoken English, Arabic



## Work Style:

Through experience with a variety of organizations and management style, I have developed proficiency and adapting capabilities through which I exhibit an optimum standard of performance. I am known for utmost dedication to what I do and oriented. While I perform independently with utmost ease.

# **Career Objective:**

Seeking new challenges that offer the opportunity for continued growth, responsibility, and financial stability and to apply expertise for the good of the company.

## Experience:

- 2009 DR. Tariq Hospital as Receptionist.
- 2010-2016 worked in M.R.S Corporation as an employee (commercial export and import assistance).
- 2017- Jan 2018 worked in Must world corporation as an employee (commercial export and import assistance) and also (merchant assistance). Actually M.R.S corporation is closed and shifted to Must world corporation with limited work major and staff.
- 2018 Nov-2019 Jan worked in Gulf Customer Experience as call center agent.

My job responsibilities include, but not limited to:

Using a variety of software package to produce word processed correspondence and documents, spreadsheet and database in both Arabic and English, by using excel access and other program.

- Manage export responsibilities according to set deadlines.
- Responsible for preparing all air and sea shipment and Customs-compliance documentation for both Exports and Import such as Commercial invoices (CI), Packing List (PL), Shipping Intrusions (SI), Forwarder Cargo Receipt (FCR), Container Load Plan (CLP), Bahrain Free Trade Agreement (BFTA), LCL and FCL shipment etc... which are required for customs and payments.
- Dealing with the mother cooperation which is located I China to get more details for the all shipments for the seasons.
- Dealing with other department "Merchandising Team" accordingly to plan for monthly and weekly shipment and cargo planning.
- Assist Chief Financial Officer "CFO" export manager with financial duties regarding export processing in an effective and responsibility way.
- Maintain a high degree of ethical relationship with internal and external Clint, shipping and logistic company as Maersk and APL and Forwarders ass "Damco".
- Well organized and capable of working independently.
- Arranging and coordinating meeting.
- Sorting, distributing mail and dealing with incoming mail and deicing on priorities.
- following various communication scripts when speaking to a caller.
- Generate customer interest in the company's products or services.

### Personal skills:

- Working: ability to write in a board range of letters, and commercial correspondence.
- Oral: good communication skills gained from working within a team.
- Computing: confident working knowledge of the internet and emails, Microsoft office

I am well organized, able to plan my own work, manage pressure and conflicting demands and priorities tasks, ability to communicate with effectively both in writing and orally with a wide range of people from external customer to senior management. Tact and discretion dealing with difficult callers, confident telephone manner, ability to work in my own initiative, reliability and honesty.

#### **Education:**

2003-3006	AL-Ahed AL-Zaher Secondary School	Science Secondary Certificate
2006-2008	University Of Bahrain	Diploma In Information System
2009	Bahrain International Retailing Development Center	Certificate in Retailing